And I'll call it over the regular schedule of the meeting of my
city council for Tuesday March 3rd, 2026.
Two public input on scheduled personal appearances.
We have one that's run a little late, so once he gets here, we'll add him on for
his three minutes.
Number three, discussion of possible action.
A, three, a, claims list.
Much to approve.
Right.
Three, b, minutes, and the February 17th, 2026 regular meeting.
Most to approve.
Sorry.
All right.
Three, c, minutes from the February 24th, 2026 regular meeting.
Most to approve.
Second.
All right.
Three, d, award, broker agent of record for property and casualty.
Insurance to Brown and Brown, insurance.
Mr. Kristi Gillley.
December 12th, we sent out an RFP for a property and casualty.
Brokerage, service services.
Brown and Brown, insurance, was the only bitter.
And after reviewing the approval, we've elected to make the Marnu broker a record.
They will accept the standard commission rate that each insurer provides and charge no additional
fees for service.
Make motion approved.
Second.
All right.
Five.
Thank you.
Three, e.
Vote on the revised airport fee schedule and recommended by the airport.
Four more.
Grab the bill.
Some of these that I believe Gill had brought up a while back.
But the main ones that we needed to take back to the airport board were barrel fuel.
So basically the state comes in and tests our fuel in our tanks out there and they store it
in 50 gallon barrels.
We've had several stockpiled, but I think we're down to maybe one.
So one of the questions that was asked when I got out there was who we sell it to,
how much do we sell it, but the board finally agreed to sell the state, the barrel fuel from
the state testing at cost plus a dollar gallon.
So if I know some other departments can use it, Tyler would be threatening from wrong.
Is it just the parks or utilities or you tell you utilities use it and we will just give it to them
I mean they just come and get it when I'm not honestly about not sure what they use it on but
We just feel like it's
We don't like storing it out there so we can sell it as quick as we can get it. That would be better
But if our guys can use it they can use it that free your cost
We've had several people ask for courts of oil. So I think we're going to start carrying some courts of oil out there
Just I mean it's minor stuff some pilots coming in and ask ask for so we've added that cost on there
Concessions so that's going to be snacks things like that and we've thrown around several ideas and popcorn stuff
I mean that'll be kind of complimentary but
Pop we even thought like in the in the mission but that's it again. That's just been in the discussion
But we do right now. We do have snacks out there. So we just need to this set cost the board agreed to that
So
Second or third is
We change the name of the credit card service fee to convenience fee part of stakes to actually so that's going to change
Third we added we added as an insufficient funds fee of $25
The board recommended that we've removed
Rental cars because we
Don't
Deal with Rental cars so much while that was on there, but we've removed that
So there's just the new four items would be
Barrel fuel
price
Change the name of the credit card service fee convenience fee to a convenience fee
Add sufficient fund fee at $25
And we removed the Rental car fee so the list you have in front of you would be the finalized list if you approved for all our
Fees out at the airport
Three out ordinance twenty twenty six dashes you're right the minute chapter twelve
I'm going to board and says add article 11
The American marijuana businesses and the ad
the following section 12-232 definitions 12.12-233 general requirements 12-234 methamyr 1 in the
spin trees 12-235 commercial medical marijuana growing and processing facilities 12-236
methamyr 1 in wholesale and storage facilities 12-237 PLT and reserveing section 12-238 to 12-308
to establish medical marijuana business regulations 12-236 conducting fees for medical marijuana business permits
providing for enforcement, penalties, severability, and declaring and effective date.
This is the... So, will the answer to this?
Chris is here too.
No, I would... You know, when all this came about, when all this came about, I would say the state
put the cart for the horse and things have kind of gone backwards, so we really didn't know
what we needed to look forward and things like that, but since we've figured it out and we've never
had a fee for any of this. So, when they come, we had to go do a live safety for their renewal to OMMA.
I mean, it's just three of charge, you know, when the state's charging them, you know, X amount.
So, and there's a lot to look at. There's a lot of life safety in some of those facilities.
I don't know the ins and outs of how they process it or do it, but a couple of these,
I guess that's all it's left, is a couple of these facilities. I mean, it's an in-depth process,
how they make this stuff.
I would say that well damn recommended at $1500, but these steps are very clear and the intervals are clear
and we can all clear what we're out. We can see we can only justify about $700.
Anything in there that allows the charge of the city's sales tax on it?
How do you find it?
We should, but we can't.
Of course, we found it on the glass.
I'm important.
When we do these inspections,
it's me sometimes me in Chris and then Chris Randolph,
and then Harder Prompt's always there too.
So it takes several departments to go and open one up
and then we have them renew there.
How long do you spend at one of these?
It could be...
It kind of...
We spent 30 minutes, you know.
It's just long enough to get the munchies.
Long enough to smell like this stuff when you walk out.
But it just depends on...
I mean, I was mentioned in names, but one that's been here for a while.
We were there a couple hours because there were so many deficiencies out there,
and they ended up having to do bringing in some type of room that they processed in,
which was a new regulation.
And it wasn't a regulation when they started.
So they had a jump through a bunch of hoops not on our end,
but the states end that we were involved in making sure that they got that.
And when they got it, we had to go make sure they got it.
And then you have the information to state departments.
So all new renewals will fall under this.
Nobody's grandfathered, and then that by it.
It's not like just for new people.
No, this was...
This is for the...
Any inspections correctly, Misty?
If this is for all the inspections that we have to do.
Yeah.
There's another choice.
There's a lot of...
That's a good choice.
That would be part of the stuff.
But I believe it's because of classified as medicine.
So the 750 would all lump in your license and then for us to go out and do it all together.
To answer a lot of questions.
No by it's grandfathered.
Any time.
Does that renew each year, right?
So no by it's grandfathered.
Anybody that gets to renew from this point forward.
We're going to fall under this.
Even if they're already here.
And established.
Okay.
And I think it was a process and I think we only have a couple now that it's just the
dispensaries that in those are fairly easy to dispensaries are just kind of like first life safety
staff that I think that was a pleasure to see them.
I mean, I know we get ready ourselves back.
Yes, we hear time out of an additional sense of text.
I know we get ourselves back, but I'm talking about four of them out of my own specifically.
Is that it?
Okay.
3G.
Board is 2026-09.
I mean, each after six buildings and building regulations are equal one.
In general, section six, dash 13.
Permits and fees of the code of ordinances to reflect really amended fees.
Permitting inspections and buildings.
Providing set of buildings and establishing an effective date.
We're comparable.
And I kind of taken consideration.
I didn't want to raise them too high because I know 10-15 years ago we went from
I think it's $25-100 or $100 overnight.
We found that a lot of people and then we didn't have a penalty fee.
That's kind of a profit of that.
But that was two.
much I came back and I lowered it to basically what it is now. $50 for inspection. So what
we're proposing I didn't want to put people out I guess more on a commercial I feel like
if you're doing a commercial build then you probably have you should probably pay for the fees
that we you get a little bit more increase than the residential residential you get some people
on fixed budget and things like that and it's tough on but like she's like Misty said it's
been probably over 10 years since we've actually raised the inspection mechanical plumbing
inspection fees and if you look and so there's a entity Oklahoma Uniform Building Code Commission
that requires and this was kind of about probably seven years ago requires a $4 state fee that
funds their their entity in Oklahoma City for every permit that you issue and that's across
every town does it across the state. What I found was they charged $4 we can charge up to $4
$50 in 50 cents so I'm proposing $4.50 for the OEBCC state fee and then the 50 cents would go into
the general or I'll let's make put it in. I think this is reasonable as much as you know we're not
raising very much $25 and $5 for your MEP inspections motion we approve. Hi thank you okay
right I say we had a public speaker to want to come to speak first three minutes and he's arrived
so Jake showed us a time this is Mr. Jake Merrick and he is a candidate for a government of Oklahoma
and he's doing a Route 66 run he started yesterday he's yesterday yeah he's starting quipe off
in the state line yesterday I bought a backster and ran through my amant today but he'll be going
across the state through May. May 6th. Yeah, 66 days. Yeah, so thank you for the time.
I just wanted to come out and you know, saw bless you. He was with me at the launch yesterday
so we're running across the state and the goal is to just connect with as many people as possible.
And so this is perfect to connect with you guys just to want to do myself, Jake Merrick.
You can follow the run at cjcrun.com or Jake Merrick for governor.com.
But you know, I am running as a conservative Republican and I want to see, I believe in limited government.
I believe in keeping government in its lane and so that's what I am working on.
And DHS has been one of our main focus that we adopted at DHS and so we want to refine the child welfare system
and then OTA and talking to several people around here about GRDA.
And there's a lot of different agencies that I think can work on keeping them in the lane to maximize freedom,
just kind of basic conservative principles.
You know, we're focusing on all the big issues that people are talking about.
We're concerned about education and the green energy and just was out of meeting earlier today about the high voltage lines that are passing through the country.
So lots of concerns about that and I'm concerned about that as well.
But yeah, I just really just want to do myself.
You can check out cjcrun.com and follow that or Jake Merrick for governor.com and reach out if you have any questions.
But we're kind of is canvassing the whole state and making some amazing progress.
I'm not taking any lobbyist or PAC money.
So I'm completely independently funded by not by myself, but by the people of Oklahoma.
And so the individual donations from people and not the corporations or PACs or special interest groups.
So that the goal is to get in that seat with no strings or hooks attached so we can really really work on true change.
So yeah, that's the just of it.
But I'll stick around here until after the meeting and answer any questions and meet you guys.
Appreciate the time.
Sure.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Nancy Connor here.
Item four.
The new business of any which the residents of the posting of this agenda.
Five staff reports.
Six mayor council community announcements.
I'll take this time just because we can never do this enough, but just to think, thank our city employees, you guys are doing a great job.
We appreciate all of you. You make our jobs easier. So, no, if you ever need anything from us, we're here for you.
Because you're here for us. So, thank you all for what you do. We appreciate it.
Thanks community, start to really recognize your efforts as well.
Seven, City Manager Communications. Yes, sir.
Eight, this means we'll now be reconvened from Council Chambers and the staff room for the purpose of executive session at the end of the MIPFA meeting.